<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.tcs.taskflow</id>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>

  <name>Task Flow</name>
  <summary>A comprehensive task management application</summary>

  <developer id="com.tcs">
    <name>TechCraft Solutions</name>
  </developer>

  <description>
    <p>Task Flow is a versatile application providing various task management utilities in one
      convenient package.</p>
    <p>Provides multiple tools for task management including:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Task organization and tracking</li>
      <li>Project management features</li>
      <li>Productivity tools</li>
      <li>And many more useful utilities</li>
    </ul>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.tcs.taskflow.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rusnakdima/TaskFlow/refs/heads/main/imgREADME/home.png</image>
      <caption>Home screen with task overview and quick access to management tools</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rusnakdima/TaskFlow/refs/heads/main/imgREADME/projects.png</image>
      <caption>Project management view for organizing and tracking multiple projects</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rusnakdima/TaskFlow/refs/heads/main/imgREADME/calendar.png</image>
      <caption>Calendar view for scheduling tasks and managing deadlines</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rusnakdima/TaskFlow/refs/heads/main/imgREADME/statistic.png</image>
      <caption>Statistics dashboard for tracking productivity and task completion</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rusnakdima/TaskFlow/refs/heads/main/imgREADME/sync.png</image>
      <caption>Synchronization settings for cloud storage and cross-device access</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>ProjectManagement</category>
  </categories>

  <keywords>
    <keyword>task</keyword>
    <keyword>management</keyword>
    <keyword>productivity</keyword>
    <keyword>organizer</keyword>
  </keywords>

  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/rusnakdima/TaskFlow</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/rusnakdima/TaskFlow/issues</url>

  <provides>
    <binary>taskflow</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="0.9.2" date="2026-01-27">
      <description>
        <p>Included both private and shared tasks in the calendar display.</p>
        <p>Implemented a 5-second task highlight effect when redirecting from the calendar to the task
          list.</p>
        <p>Added automatic scrolling to ensure the target task is within the visible area upon
          redirection.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.1" date="2026-01-26">
      <description>
        <p>Fixed 404 error when navigating to Admin page from header menu.</p>
        <p>Fixed Rust backend compilation error regarding missing codeExpiresAt field.</p>
        <p>Added codeExpiresAt field to user models for email verification support.</p>
        <p>Implemented #[serde(default)] for user model fields to ensure backward compatibility with
          existing database records and fix login redirect loops.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.0" date="2026-01-16">
      <description>
        <p>Enhanced real-time data synchronization with WebSocket integration for improved
          collaborative task management and shared project updates.</p>
        <p>Implemented Angular signals throughout the application for better reactivity and
          performance in task management components.</p>
        <p>Added comprehensive admin features including category records management and bulk
          selection capabilities for better data administration.</p>
        <p>Improved task sharing functionality with enhanced privacy controls, ownership
          verification, and query parameter handling.</p>
        <p>Refactored routing system with flattened nested routes and enhanced component safety for
          better navigation experience.</p>
        <p>Added sync metadata support across statistics, tasks, and subtasks for better data
          tracking and synchronization.</p>
        <p>Integrated activity logging system for comprehensive task activity monitoring and history
          tracking.</p>
        <p>Enhanced form validation and UI responsiveness with improved date handling, optional
          fields, and better mobile layouts.</p>
        <p>Optimized API services with flexible filter parameters and standardized method calls for
          improved maintainability.</p>
        <p>Updated dependencies and Rust code formatting for better performance and security.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.0" date="2026-01-08">
      <description>
        <p>Enhanced user experience with mobile-responsive calendar layout and improved component
          designs</p>
        <p>Added responsive calendar grid for mobile devices with touch-friendly interface</p>
        <p>Simplified admin view layout structure for better performance</p>
        <p>Improved component responsiveness and removed redundant creator information</p>
        <p>Implemented reactive syncing status handling in header</p>
        <p>Redesigned about page with modern card-based layout</p>
        <p>Enhanced authentication with local data caching</p>
        <p>Added password visibility toggles and improved form controls</p>
        <p>Updated styling and layout consistency across components</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.4" date="2026-01-05">
      <description>
        <p>Added max height and vertical scroll to categories list in stats page</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.3" date="2025-12-21">
      <description>
        <p>Changed the application collector via Github Action</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.2" date="2025-12-21">
      <description>
        <p>The style of the progress bar in the Todo and Task elements has been changed: segments of
          each status are now displayed.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.1" date="2025-12-13">
      <description>
        <p>Changed the logic for storing authorization</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.0" date="2025-12-09">
      <description>
        <p>Changed the code styles in rust</p>
        <p>Deep-link listening code removed</p>
        <p>Added the authorization verification feature to all pages</p>
        <p>The logic of downloading a new version of the application has been changed</p>
        <p>The page layout has been changed</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.6.2" date="2025-11-30">
      <description>
        <p>Fixed an issue with opening a page with subtasks after deletion</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.6.1" date="2025-11-30">
      <description>
        <p>Fixed an error loading data for statistics and data synchronization</p>
        <p>Fixed the Flatpak collector app via Github Action</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.6.0" date="2025-11-30">
      <description>
        <p>Changed the types of statuses for tasks/subtasks</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.5.0" date="2025-11-24">
      <description>
        <p>The description field in the task/subtask management forms is now optional.</p>
        <p>Changed the position and size of the radio button for tasks/subtasks.</p>
        <p>Added logic for the end date field: now it can only be specified if there is a start
          date, if the start date is deleted, then the end date of the task/subtask is also deleted,
          and now you cannot select the end date before the start date.</p>
        <p>Added a date deletion button in the form for editing tasks/subtasks.</p>
        <p>Implemented logic so that new tasks/subtasks are shown first.</p>
        <p>Added logic for sorting tasks/subtasks so that completed entries are after those not
          completed in the list.</p>
        <p>The read-only property is set for fields with dates.</p>
        <p>Fixed block markup on the task page.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.0" date="2025-08-20">
      <description>
        <p>Added new features and improved functionality</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
